the Peruvian skulls and
>> No, before I thought Oh, go ahead.
Sorry.
>> No, go ahead.
>> Oh, before I thought that, but um cuz
like there's skulls in China that were
originally mistaken for chromagnet and
Neanderthal and stuff like old and now
they say they're artificially modified
by people. But
>> no, I think um could you pull up the
image for Chiari malfformation? It's the
It's got two heads with one circled like
two cat scans.
>> Well, I was talking about the brain
falling down into the thing.
>> They believe that this is a problem from
Neanderthal andor Denise and mingling
with us. Skull too small, brain too big.
So now if you have this consistent
problem, you've got to always got
pressure on the brain.
>> See how it's pops down there? You've
always got this pressure on the brain.
>> Now imagine if you
>> you might drill holes in your head. Like
you've seen all the truncation that's
happened down there. There's an image of
that. Yep. And then or you might
elongate the back of the skull every
generation so that your kids don't have
the same [ __ ] headaches grandpa did.
>> And so it becomes a thing that and this
is why if you check out South America
Paracus is insane this way. They have so
many things. The polyactyli
the elongated skulls the tffonation.
There's a thing. Could you pull up the
Inca bone one where your skulls melt?
The plates in the skull melt in the
back. If there is stress or a lack of
equilibrium, you'll end up what they
call firmian bones. Ones in the back are
wormyian bones. The ones in the back are
so pronounced. Um, the are called Inca
bones because they happen mostly in Inca
territory. You also see in Easter
Island, the Pacific Northwest, and in
Asia. But this part of the skull right
there, um, there's one that's got a
Neanderthal that shows this, too.
Neanderthalss have the same issue.
There's another one. And there's an
island. Uh oh, Jesus. Um
but yeah, the uh Sorry, there's Yeah,
there's one
>> my own head right now.
>> There's one with white text at the
bottom, Jamie. Sorry. Um but yeah,
Neanderthal had it. Um and it's a uh
again, it's from a lack of equilibrium.
They say it's from the brain and the
skull, not quite fitting.
>> That makes sense.
>> I think in South America, I think that
they were mingling different bloodlines.
them the the same as you can look at a
guy that plays Reacher and tell that
he's probably got more Neanderthal in
him than I do. And they would mingle
these bloodlines and then they would get
all kinds of different Yeah, there's a
Neanderthal one. Um they would get all
kinds of different genetic variations.
And I think some of these were bad, but
some of them were honored. Like you've
seen the jaguar people of the Mech.
>> Okay. Um you ever seen uh could you pull
up the the dental dysplasia one? The kid
with the two fangs. There's there's
dental things. It'll make you grow fangs
as a child. And it also quite often will
give you a hair lip. Jaguar.
>> Whoa. And so like if you look Yeah.
And so like
>> what do you think that's from?
>> Again, this is from
>> Is that some ancient [ __ ] where people
used to have teeth like that?
>> It's it's DNA there. They again when we
crossmingle DNA. Um there should be one
uh right there about the mouths with the
uh paper. Sorry, I have to pull up the
exact
>> right. But those teeth, that's not in
any other human primate that we've ever
found.
>> No, it's it happens in ours. But with
>> So, it's just a mal foration.
>> A malf for that. And we have a lot of
that like the uh some people just keep
growing teeth. Right.
>> Right.
>> Um you know, or you get different bones
in the head. Um different shapes of the
skull.
>> I've seen the skulls, ancient skulls
with rows of teeth.
>> Yeah. Yeah. some of those um like they
don't know for sure how many of those
are legit, but the um there's there's
definitely no question that these things
happen. That's again the real problem
with this is becomes a cover up. Like a
little bit ago I mentioned that they
were all these elongated schools in the
Pacific Northwest. um Mount Coffin in
Long View, Washington. When Colonel
Charles Wilks or Lieutenant Charles
Wils, whose father happened to be a
member of the Skull and Bone Society in
England, when he got to Long View,
Washington, he saw Mount Coffin, this
place where they had these above ground
burials, and there were 3,000 of them,
all of them supposedly would have had
elongated skulls because again, if you
don't have an elongated skull in that
neck of the woods, you weren't a
freeborn person. And this was you had to
be noble to be buried there. 3,000
elongated skulls. When he left this
campfire accidentally burnt the place
down, all those skulls disappeared. Um,
that image that he Jamie skipped past a
little bit goes just a dude sitting on
pile of bones. This is an Indian burial
ground and they were just looting the
things and selling them left and right.
>> Where do you think those things are?
>> In people's house, people's hands.
>> Well, I've never heard of a story of a
person having an elongated skull in
their private collection. I have a
couple of people that have commented on
my videos saying like, "I saw one at so
and so's house in 1978, but
>> but here but I'll give you the smoking
gun though, right? If you're like some
Rockefeller type guy, you got a mansion
in Rhode Island."
>> It's funny you brought up Rockefeller in
the 30s when T down in Paracas, he he
starts putting out, hey, we've got these
elongated skulls down there and I need
money. He was getting $300 a year to
take care of them. Rockefeller gets wind
and history says flat out he took an
unexpected trip to Peru. He dropped
three grand and walked back with four
bundles. Now according to
>> that's it. Three grand.
>> Yeah. And four four grave bundles.
That's 10 times what Tel was getting a
year. 10 times what the guy was getting
a year to take care of all of them. He
coughs up four out of like 300 bundles.
Now those four bundles were supposedly
displayed at the Met. Supposedly
displayed at the National History Museum
in New York. No photos exist. No
drawings exist. They may have been
repatriated. They may not have been
repatriated. Depends on who you ask. The
AI will run you in a damn circle of
going with it. At the end of the day, we
don't know which four they what they
look like. But I can tell you this much.
There's about 300 of those bundles to
pick from. Do you think Rockefell if one
of them had great big old devil horns
and a third eye, do you think
Rockefeller left it or took it with him?
Did [ __ ] no-brainer [ __ ] Right.
Right.
>> So, the best of the best always gone.
And as soon when Rockefeller found out
that he couldn't go get the ones in the
Pacific Northwest anymore, but there was
some somewhere else, he ran there. And
right now, you sent me the video just a
little bit ago. But this is more there.
These skulls are disappearing off the
shelves in the museums right now.
>> Yeah.
>> Right as we speak. This this cover up.
There's this cover up. You I'm sure
you've seen the map. Um it a 100 years
ago they wrote drew a map of artificial
cranial deformation and then like 10
years ago they made another one. both of
these on peer-reviewed papers and the
older map has more information. There's
more the more areas they've erased. The
island of Newi had it. Ancient Hawaiian
people had about 8.9% of them that they
dig up had elongated skulls. Nobody
[ __ ] talks about that. Nobody knows
about it. If you want to go look at it,
the answer is no.
>> When you say ancient, like what year?
>> Not sure. But when they dig them up and
they start doing at prehistoric they
call it, but prehistoric in Hawaii, you
know, maybe a thousand years ago.
>> Wow. So this is all over the world
people are doing that. Well yeah that
what you're saying about the brain size
and the the base of the brain completely
makes sense.
>> Thank you. I I mean to me it seems like
the most smoke and it not only does it
smoking gun it's like it coincides with
human evolution because what would be
imagine you've got a Neanderthal and a
homo sapiion and they're talking to each
other trying to figure out a problem and
they both walk away from that with like
mad respect for the other person's
ability to see what they don't. wouldn't
they want to mingle that?
So like uh Jamie, could you pull that
picture that I got of the uh that family
tree? Um it's just it's like an empty
blank white family tree and then right
after it's the like imagine if you were
trying to make a symbol to tell
everybody, hey, this is where we mingle
bloodlines. So like this is a standard
kind of thing, right? And could you pull
up that condalabra next? should be like
>> um sorry
>> uh that same symbol basically with the
condal labra of the Andes you've seen
that right the
condal labra of the Andes is visible 12
miles out to sea okay um
if you think we're trying to draw the
draw we're trying to draw the mingling
of of bloodlines and here's a symbol of
where we're doing it [ __ ] doesn't I
mean does that kind of look uncanny. And
then could you pull up that Paracus
textile, Jamie? This one even wore. This
is when they buried people in paracus.
This was they'd put them in these
textiles. And this one textile. Look,
they're back. They look at what that try
to translate that and keep in mind what
I was just telling you. Okay. It looks
like a monkey on either side and then a
person in the middle. And it looks like
there's some sort of a transference of
something through the top of their
heads. Well, that's upside down.
>> Yeah, that's upside down. Well, there's
first of all, it looks like they did
DMT.
>> Well, clearly
>> it looks like they
>> This is Hours of Iawaska right there,
buddy.
>> 100% they were on DMT. Um, but that does
look like two monkeys, right? It looks
like they have tails,
>> doesn't it?
>> Yeah, it does.
>> And then the one in the middle looks
like the bad [ __ ] That's the
boss.
>> That's pregnant.
>> I've met that guy before.
>> You have?
>> I have. I met that guy. I met that guy
over there. But you see that notice in
the middle of the thing, he's got a
something in his tummy.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Um I mean, if you think about the same
line of reasoning, we're mixing
different blood lines to make something
more. That image kind of seems to
>> Also, they always have three fingers and
three toes. And then you get to the
tridactyl mummies.
>> I do. Yeah, look at the monkeys. I don't
know what to think about the tridactyl
mummies.
>> Neither do I. It's honestly like um I'm
of the opinion now that I think that the
genetic stuff they were doing in South
America down in Peru created a lot of
artificial created a lot of natural
weird problems and some of them would be
um like misshapen skulls and then I
think they would wrap the heads to
artificially modify them and I think
that's why down there they get so crazy
looking is because it's a combination of
genetics and of artificially playing
with it. Okay.
>> The rest of the world, they don't get
that con.
>> So, do you think maybe they had like a
bulbous roundish head but extra large?
Because there's those skulls as well
that seem to be not deformed, but they
do have a larger brain capacity.
>> Yeah. Though the ones that are bulbous
in the back, those are um that's the
most common type of cranial deformation
that you see. It's what um conly skull,
the chief that I was showing you. Um
it's uh Can you pull that one up,
please, Jamie? Sorry.
>> So, bulbous in the back. Bulbous. Yeah.
That's huge. Yeah. And that again that
would keep it. And now notice even back
a 100 years ago that picture that he was
just showing that uh
>> the other photograph. Why isn't his
skull elongated?
>> Well, it's hard to tell because he's
looking straight on. It could be.
>> All of the all of the artistic work of
him is lacking that for some reason.
>> Right. But couldn't you see that if some
Well, that one looks pretty elongated.
>> God, go back to that. That's crazy.
Imagine meeting those dudes. You'd be
like, "Yo, what are you?"
>> Check check.
>> And look, they're doing it to the baby
right there.
>> Oh, the poor kid. Oh, imagine being a
baby. You're [ __ ] strapped into that
thing.
>> Oh, man. Dave's uh in this book here, it
quotes from a book called A Story That
Used to be Required Reading up where I
live. And uh the guy that witnessed
them, one of these kids being their
headbinding, it said that their eyes
bulged out of their skull like a mouse
caught in a trap.
>> Oh my god. So when you think about that
honestly, but if your kid was going to
have migraines incessantly for the rest
of their life, you might just do that
anyway.
>> Yeah, I guess they had to do it if
you're right. If you're right about the
base of the brain, which kind of tracks
it,
>> but it to me the the the capacity of the
skulls being so much larger and some of
the Peruvian skulls is weird.